<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[FDP Communications]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[FDP Communications]]></description>
        <link>http://fdpcommunication.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 04:02:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://fdpcommunication.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 04:02:04 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Message from Direk Alfredo Ongleo of the short film "Pormalin"]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FY-JNvOzOz4M%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DY-JNvOzOz4M&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FY-JNvOzOz4M%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=a715cf41cc93453ca338d350cd26f87b&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y-JNvOzOz4M&amp;feature=share</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">27bd679e-c964-49a7-832a-8c7fa10f1eff</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 04:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CINEMALAYA FEATURES CITIZEN JAKE, SMALLER AND SMALLER CIRCLES, AND OTHERS IN INDIE NATION]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>PRESS RELEASE</strong></p>,<p><strong>July 31, 2018</strong></p>,<h1><strong>CINEMALAYA FEATURES CITIZEN JAKE, SMALLER AND SMALLER CIRCLES, AND OTHERS IN INDIE NATION</strong></h1>,<p><strong>THE Cinemalaya's special section Indie Nation will let film enthusiasts cross out the indie films which they may have missed on their regular screening at the cinema from their must-watch checklist. This component of the Cinemalaya Philippine Independent Film Festival features seven indie films that made buzz and gained international recognition.</strong></p>,<p><strong>The featured indie films include: “Citizen Jake” by Mike de Leon; “Chedeng &amp; Apple” by Rae Red and Fatrick Tabada; “Delia And Sammy” by Therese Cayaba; “Gusto Kita With All My Hypothalamus” by Dwein Baltazar; “Mga Mister Ni Rosario” by Alpha Habon; “Smaller And Smaller Circles” by Raya Martin; “Nervous Translation” by Shireen Seno; “Manggagarab (Man With Sickle)” by Kyle Fermindoza; and, “Bomba (The Bomb)” by Ralston Gonzales Jover.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cf2db0ef-a61e-4459-9f95-4839efe17203.jpg">,<p><strong>Directed by Mike De Leon, “Citizen Jake” is a personal saga of a Filipino and his struggles with the contradictions within his own social class and the demands of a dysfunctional political family in a Third World nation. The film features actors Cherie Gil, Dina Bonnevie, Luis Alandy, Gabby Eigenmann, Max Collins, Teroy Guzman, and Nonie Buencamino, with journalist Atom Araullo as Citizen Jake.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/5a42514e-d778-439d-bf99-6bf6452cdd13.jpg">,<p><strong>“Chedeng &amp; Apple,” which is co-directed by Rae Red and Fatrick Tabada, is a comic film about two friends who are both in their 60s. In the wake of her husband's death, 66-yeard-old Chedeng decides to come out of the closet, while her 63-year-old best friend Apple beheads her live-in partner in a fit of rage. With a severed head placed inside a Louis Vuitton bag, the two elderly women together set off an adventure to find Chedeng's ex-girlfriend. It stars Gloria Diaz, Elizabeth Oropesa and Anthony Falcon.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/53e3a5e5-c033-4146-bd45-8b8e7cdf238c.jpg">,<p><strong>When she learns about her terminal illness, faded and forgotten actress Delia has to find family to take care and leave her difficult husband Sammy with, before she dies in comedy-drama film “Delia and Sammy.” Directed by Therese Cayaba, the film features Rosemarie Gil, Jaime Fabregas, and Nico Antonio.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/955dd008-9844-4e20-850a-93f0111f3637.jpg">,<p><strong>In “Gusto Kita With All My Hypothalamus,” director Dwein Baltazar explores the intertwined fate of four men, who all long for a mysterious girl named Aileen. Actors Nicco Manalo, Dylan Ray Talon, Soliman Cruz and Anthony Falcon bring this romantic film to life.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/fed4bbf1-2b50-4d1d-ba8f-b7e85fcf0893.jpg">,<p><strong>“Mga Mister ni Rosario” by Alpha Habon is about Yogi Juan, the Philippine Showbiz’s Golden Boy who takes every role seriously, and his devoted housewife Sari who supports him and role-plays along. But what will happen when Yogi takes the role is a serial killer, can Sari revise the morbid fate that awaits her? he film stars Joross Gamboa, Kate Alejandrino, Kim Molina, Dax Carnay, Rap Robes, and Kiki Baento.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/593f55f3-920c-471e-9a54-e30a8d12048b.jpg">,<p><strong>In “Smaller and Smaller Circles” by Raya Martin, a serial killer in Payatas leaves the bodies of young boys in the dump as two Jesuit priests try to solve the murders. Adapted from the award-winning novel of F.H. Batacan, it features Nonie Buencamino, Sid Lucero, Carla Humphries, Gladys Reyes, Raffy Tejada, Bembol Rocco, and TJ Trinidad.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/347a3a74-2a39-4021-957b-c5ad0d2defb7.jpg">,<p><strong>Director Shireen Seno gives voice to eight-year-old Yael who prefers to be by herself, yet deeep down longs to be heard in “Nervous Translation.” In the film, the shy young girl prefers writing letters instead of performing dances. When she hears an advertisement for a pen that will give her a wonderful life, she decides to spend all her savings to buy it.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3f26bd42-dcb7-4788-a96f-c1f93d0089fd.jpg">,<p><strong>Directed by Kyle Fermindoza, “Manggagarab” tells about father Gabriel and daughter Celie who has been living peacefully in the mountains. Even though he struggles to provide for his daughter, everything seems normal until the past starts crawling in and devouring Gabriel.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/8ba0e4be-ad8a-4fa8-9bd5-4797385e8c1e.jpg">,<p><strong>In “Bomba,” actor Allen Dizon plays a deaf-mute in his 40s who is having an affair with a 16-year-old girl (played by Angeli Nicole Sanoy). Director Ralston Gonzales Jover captures the deafening silent existence that is dying to explode.</strong></p>,<p><strong>Watch all these indie films at the Cinemalaya, happening on August 3 to 12, at the CCP theaters. For more information, visit <a href="http://www.cinemalaya.org/">www.cinemalaya.org</a> or <a href="http://www.culturalcenter.gov.ph./">www.culturalcenter.gov.ph.</a> You may also call CCP Media Arts at 832-1125 local 1704 to 1705 and the CCP Box Office at 832-3704. Or follow the Cinemalaya Facebook and Instagram accounts.</strong></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/adaeba38-1796-487d-b643-c715d30d6017.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://fdpcommunication.com/cinemalaya-features-citizen-jake-smaller-and-smaller-circle/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c97229d3-53b5-4e14-8c54-9902c0c040ab</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 04:02:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[‎Tips for reluctant meditators]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>&lrm;Tips for reluctant meditators</h1><p>&lrm;No time for mindfulness? This man can help. Tap to read how.</p><img src="https://is4-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Video125/v4/8a/22/eb/8a22eb30-9b81-d1ed-7f6a-dcb907a8490f/Job0ad02f74-28aa-44cf-8bd8-53e3c5e5c7a9-100619276-PreviewImage_preview_image_nonvideo_sdr-Time1530652864518.png/1200x630bb.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://itunes.apple.com/ph/story/id1331264933</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1c75a3e2-be5b-4b89-915d-b2205b791bd0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 07:57:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[‎Real friendships take time]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>&lrm;Real friendships take time</h1><p>&lrm;Learn about Real friendships take time on App Store.</p><img src="https://is2-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Features118/v4/58/8e/ab/588eab6f-db78-e2f2-882c-fbb3a104a5c6/source/1200x630.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://itunes.apple.com/ph/story/id1408376514</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a37b186e-b38c-4ddc-8d4c-739c55f81564</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 03:55:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>